The kettle and the idol
Now then, please give a cute title call.
My three main elements!
Yes, this is the famous corner. This is the corner where we ask you to introduce the sealed elements that affirm you.
I hope you will watch this corner and get to know Ms. Sakamoto more deeply.
Please tell us about your sealing factor. Please tell us about the sealing factor.
Please tell us about the sealing factor.
Yes!
1. active 2. let me be free 3. inspiration
Oh! It's like a three-step house.
It's like the anticipation is getting higher and higher.
I'm glad.
I have other hobbies, and I love to go out and do things rather than staying inside.
Among my hobbies, I really like sea fishing,
That's right. So, when people think of Mr. Sakamoto, they think of fishing.
Yes, that's right. I like fishing and I like the sea,
Whenever he has a day off, he goes to the sea to fish,
If it is summer, he goes to the sea and drives a water bike.
I'm quite often barbecuing on the beach where I can see the ocean,
I guess I'm active.
Do you sometimes put fishing in between work?
I haven't done it in a day yet,
When I catch a big fish or an extra-large one, I brag about it to the other members.
What? When did you say that in the spring?
We had a big show coming up, and we had a lot of rehearsal work to do,
Even when you have just one day off,
What? I would say, "You can go,
I get quite a few surprises. Even the managers are surprised.
I see.
But in terms of your current use, you have been active in the ocean,
Is there anything else you are into or would like to do in the future outside of the ocean?
Other than the ocean, I really like to collect votive offerings,
I also like to breathe the air of various shrines and temples.
I like to breathe the clean air of the place where I live,
When I travel, I like to go to famous shrines,
Nowadays, there are many shrines where the celebrants are very cute,Nowadays, there are many shrines with very cute celebrants,
So, I put those places on Google Maps as landmarks,
Even in Tokyo, I sometimes go to a shrine that I find nearby if I am on site today.
I see.
Are the other members not active?
Mr. Sakamoto's point of view.
It depends on the members,
I met Hoka Akimoto in Nagoya, and she is a sea woman of the same kind,
Hoka-chan is a mogul.
Hoka is a licensed scuba diver and specializes in moguls,
I am from above.
We have the same feeling of watching and catching fish,
We have the ocean in common,
Nao Sakura also loves the great outdoors,
We have private trips to Okinawa and so on,
We have been talking about going fishing for a long time,
Last year, I went fishing with Nagoya for the first time,
I had heard that beginners can catch a lot of fish,
I had heard that beginners can catch a lot of fish, but I thought it was really possible.
I caught all kinds of fish,
I fished for a variety of species and caught horse mackerel,
I also caught a big one, a big one, and a big one.
It was fun.
As for Mizuki, I don't have such an active image,
But I feel like if I ask her out, she'll go,
On the contrary, I tell her that I have her take me out in the spring.
Is there anything you don't like? Is this a consultation about a problem?
That's a bit of a message, isn't it?
What is this program about?
Mr. Kogezaka
Kazuya
Saki
Mr. Can
Makoto-kun
We are pleased to present to you
Tonight's dinner wasTonight's dinner was
Sushi
Done!